nullanswer.com 2015-07-24

# nullanswer Privacy Policy

We are committed to maintaining privacy protections for our users. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Website.

BY USING THE WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

## Definitions

  * “Policy” mean this Privacy Policy.
  * “We”, “us” means the owner and the administration of the Website.
  * “User”, “you” means you, a person using the Website.
  * “Website”, “Site” means this website including programming code, databases and design. 
  * “Personal Data” means information or its combination that can be used to identify the User as an individual, such as, for example name, email address, phone number, home address.
  * “Anonymous Data” means non-personally identifiable information about an individual that alone or in combination with similar information can not be used to identify the User, for example, computer’s IP address or browsing history. 
  * “Information” means any Personal Data, Anonymous Data and/or any other information that is public by default.

## Anonymous Data Collected Automatically

We collect Anonymous Data from your browser when you use the Website.

The Website automatically collects usage information, such as your IP address and country, browser type and language, access times, version, language and type of your operating system, the number and frequency of visitors to the Website. We maintain log files of the traffic that visits the Website.

## Information We Do Not Collect

WE DO NOT COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA. We do not process and collect any Personal Data or personally identifiable information, unless you specifically decide to provide such information (such as by emailing to us). 

Your submission of any Personal Data is voluntary and you have the choice (and we urge you) not to disclose any Personal Data to us.

## Cookies

We use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate access to the Website and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of cookies, we may automatically collect Information about your online activity on the Website, such as the web pages you visit and the links you click.

We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any other way or to store any Personal Data.

For general information on cookies, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>

This Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link or advertisement points may set cookies on your computer. Some of these services may be used to track your behavior on other websites and we have no control over this.

Your web browser allows you to control and limit cookies on your computer.

## Interactions with Third-Party Log-in Services

If you use your Facebook or other third-party log-in service (“Third-Party Service”) account information to sign in to the Website, we will collect and store your Third-Party Service user ID.

We use your Information from such Third-Party Service account only in accordance with your privacy settings you have set up with that Third-Party Service.

## Why We Collect Information

We will not use or disclose the Information except as necessary or required, or out of accordance with the purpose outlined in this Policy. In any case, the Information is used anonymously in aggregation with similar information from other users of the Website for:

  * Delivering you the services and functionality that you have requested,
  * Your seamless interaction with the Website,
  * Analytical and statistical purposes,
  * Understanding of our User’s interaction with the Website,
  * Improvement and development of the Website,
  * Displaying content and advertising tailored to your interests on the Internet,
  * Enforcement of this Policy and our Terms of Use.

## Disclosure of Information

We may release the Information concerning your use of the Website:

  * When we believe in good faith that such release is appropriate to comply with the applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request (for example, pursuant to a statutory demand, subpoena, warrant or court order);
  * To enforce the Terms of Use, or any agreement between you and us;
  * To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; 
  * To protect against abusive or unlawful use of the Website;
  * To protect the rights, safety, or property of Users, or any other third parties;
  * If we reasonably believe that a situation involving danger of death or injury to any person requires disclosure;
  * In other ways described in this Policy or to which you have otherwise consented.

## With Whom We Share the Information

We may share Anonymous Data we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising on websites of third parties.

We may share aggregated Anonymous Data with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and contractors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of users of the Website and the most popular features or services accessed.

This Policy does not limit in any way our use or disclosure of Information and we reserve the right to use and disclose such Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties at our discretion.

## How Long We Retain Information

We do not retain Information that can be used to identify a browser beyond the time period necessary to complete the function for which Information was collected.

## Third-Party Websites and Services

Third parties may collect your Information. There are a number of places on or through the Website where you may click on a link to access other websites, services or web resources that are not affiliated or connected with us and do not operate under this Policy. For example, if you click on an ad or a download link, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently collect information, including your Personal Data, from you. **We advise you to check the privacy policies of all third-party websites you visit.**

We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements or place ad tags on the Websites. We do not provide any Personal Data to these companies. These third-party companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect Information about computers used to view or interact with their ads.

## Your Consent

YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO OUR PROCESSING, COLLECTION, TRANSFER, STORAGE, DISCLOSURE AND OTHER USES OF YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT INSTANCE WHEN YOU:

  * PROVIDE INFORMATION TO US THROUGH THE WEBSITE; OR
  * ACCEPT THE TERMS OF USE AND/OR USE THE WEBSITE; 

IN ADDITION, THROUGH THIS USE AND INTERACTIONS WITH THE WEBSITE, YOU SPECIFICALLY CONSENT TO OUR COLLECTION OF THE INFORMATION BY AUTOMATED MEANS, SUCH AS COOKIES OR THE INTENDED FUNCTIONALITY OF THE WEBSITE, AND TO OUR SUBSEQUENT PROCESSING AND USING OF THE INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND/OR THE TERMS OF USE, AND TO THE STORAGE AND TRANSFER OF THE INFORMATION TO LOCATIONS WHEREVER WE AND OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS HAVE FACILITIES.

## Information Concerning Children

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to use the Website. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take immediate steps to remove that information.

## Sensitive Information

We do not deal with any sensitive Information, such as related to the racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, physical or mental health or condition, crime or court records, etc.

## Information Security

We will take commercially reasonable precautions to protect Information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We process all Information using industry-standard techniques. We store the Information on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted. However, we do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to Information that we store.

## Severability and Integration

This Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and us and supersedes all previous written or oral agreements. If any part of the Policy is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.

## Changes to the Policy

We may change the Policy at any time. The most current version will always be located at this webpage. If you continue to use the Site after we make changes to the Policy, you are signifying your acceptance of the new terms. You are responsible for checking this Policy periodically for any changes.

Effective: October 27, 2014
